Everything sounds sexier in French.
Le Divorce is a drama, romance, comedy film directed by James Ivory.
While visiting her sister in Paris, a young woman finds romance
and learns her brother-in-law is a philanderer.
Isabel Walker, played by Kate Hudson.
Roxeanne de Persand, played by Naomi Watts.
Olivia Pace, played by Glenn Close.
Amélie Cosset, played by Marie-Christine Adam.
Edgar Cosset, played by Thierry Lhermitte.
Charles-Henri de Persand, played by Melvil Poupaud.
Le Divorce is a 2003 romantic comedy-drama film directed by James Ivory from a screenplay by Ruth
Prawer Jhabvala and Ivory, based on the 1997 novel of the same name by Diane Johnson.
The film explores themes of infidelity, france, police, brother-in-law, artist.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.